

INFO

Address

Ban Phan Luang,

Luang Prabang, Laos

Phone

+856 2098044162

E-mail

kylewag@me.com

EDUCATION

MA Geography

York University, Toronto

BA International Studies

DePaul University, Chicago

SOCIAL

in kyledwagner

★ t.me/kdwagner

(iii) kyledwagner

+66 80 362 0972

SKILLS

Photoshop	•	lacktriangle	•	•	•
Illustrator	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	•	lacktriangle	0
InDesign	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	0
Adobe XD	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	0	0
Sketch	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	•	•	0
HTML/CSS	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	0
Javascript	lacktriangle	0	0	0	0
Git	lacktriangle	lacktriangle	•	0	0

LANGUAGES

English	••••
Japanese	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ
Lan	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Kyle Wagner

MARKETING MANAGER & DESIGNER

SUMMARY

Marketing manager and digital designer with over four years of professional experience in Southeast Asia. Creative team player with the ability to work cross-culturally with international clients under tight deadlines. Actively learning front-end web development and UI design.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Marketing Manager @ Focus Asia

Luang Prabang

Dec 2017 - Current

Created, executed and optimized email marketing strategy with 2x weekly send rate; yielded ~20% OR with ~5% CTR. Lead marketing team to redesign and rewrite 250pg travel catalogue for increased ROI. Rebranded luxury travel sub-brand including website development, logotype design and all marketing collaterals. Produced 'Asia On Stage' booth concept for ITB 2019 with single-page microsite, branding and print media.

Web Developer and Designer @ TYPE-C

Remote

Jul 2018 - Current

Programmed 2 microsites and designed social media ads for a campaign promoting Laos to the Singaporean market. Designed and coded three websites using the SquareSpace platform for clients in Singapore. Designed a postcard concept for a video production company in Toronto.

Project Coordinator @ GIZ

Remote

Jul 2016 - Apr 2019

Managed, conceptualized and designed presentations and A3 posters together with UNESCO office for heritage protection. Developed and designed booth layout for ITB Asia in Singapore for 2 years. Built a sustainable trade show booth for Paksé Ecotourim Forum.

Marketing Coordinator @ Tiger Trail

Luang Prabang

Sep 2014 - Sep 2019

Redesigned visual communication platform including print-based signage, tour catalogues, brochures, logos, posters, business cards, and newsletters. Developed and produced original content for two responsive brand websites: Fairtrek.org and Biking-Laos.com. Conceptualized and executed an effective marketing plan, social media strategy, and brand presentation.